

DIEGO MUÑOZ BELTRÁN

CONTACT

✓ Madrid, Spain

****+34 676 640 409

○/ diegombeltran

in diegomunozbeltran

www.diegomunozbeltran.com

yo@diegomunozbeltran.com

ABOUT ME

I'm a 29 years old network engineering student in love with IT world. I spend most of my spare time looking for new amazing projects to discover. I enjoy managing bare metal servers at home, and I automate most of the things I develop, doing so in an agile way of thinking. When I'm not in front of the screen, I love watching movies, playing the electric guitar, boxing, chess and tango.

LANGUAGES

Spanish English Native

C1 (TOEIC 960/990)

WORK EXPERIENCE

DEVOPS ENGINEER, BBVA NEXT TECHNOLOGIES

Madrid, Spain — 2017-Present

Focused primarily on:

Cloud: Amazon Web Services, GCE, Azure

• Infrastructure as Code: Ansible, Terraform

• CI/CD tools: GitLabCI, Jenkins

• Container Orchestration: Docker, Kubernetes, Openshift

Agile Methodologies: Scrum, Kanban

Distributed Architectures

SYSTEM ADMINISTRATOR, BIOMEDICAL IMAGING AND INSTRUMENTATION GROUP, HOSPITAL GENERAL GREGORIO MARAÑÓN

Madrid, Spain — 2013-2017

Topics covered:

• Virtualization: VMWare Vsphere, KVM

Networking: Cisco devices, VLAN management

• Cybersecurity: Fortinet, pfSense

Monitoring: Sensu, NagiOS, Zabbix, Grafana

• Scripting: *Python, Bash*

FRONTEND DEVELOPER, FREELANCE

Madrid, Spain — 2013-2016

Some projects and technologies used:

- Asociación de Científicos Fundación Alicia Koplowitz website
 - https://www.asociaciondecientificos-fundak.org
- PSYSCAN website
 - http://www.psyscan.eu
- Tools and technologies: Drupal 7/8, Jekyll, Pelican, Ghost, HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, PHP.

EDUCATION

TELEMATIC ENGINEERING DEGREE

Escuela Técnica Superior de Ingeniería y Sistemas de Telecomunicación, Universidad Politécnica de Madrid — 2009

Part-time student

SOFT SKILLS

Leadership
Proactive Attitude
Learning
Motivation



TAGS

Linux, RHEL/CentOS/Fedora, Debian, FreeBSD, pfSense, FortiOS, Ansible, Fortinet, Terraform, Kubernetes, Openshift, Chef, Nginx, Apache, MongoDB, MySQL, MariaDB, PostgreSQL, Nagios, Grafana, Telegraf, DNS, DHCP, OpenVPN, IPSEC, iptables, AWS, EC2, S3, VMWare, Route53, ESXI, Virtualbox, Proxmox, KVM, Git, GitHub, GitLab, JIRA, Bash, Java, Go, Node.js Python, C++, Matlab, HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, BIND, Exim, Postfix, Drupal, Typo3, Ghost, Hugo, Jekyll, Pelican.

PREFERENCES

Linux, free open source software, DevOps culture, cybersecurity, auditing, pentesting, networks, cloud, infrastructure as code, automation, agile methodologies, virtualization and containerization, IoT, domotics, privacy, medicaloriented IT, learning

CERTIFICATIONS

AWS CERTIFIED SOLUTIONS ARCHITECT - ASSOCIATE

ID: 193PCVX2DN1QQTSZ Date Earned: Apr 09, 2018 Valid Through: Apr 10, 2021

COURSES

ARCHITECTING WITH AWS

Global Knowledge, 2017

VMWARE VSPHERE ICM: INSTALL, CONFIGURE AND MANAGE 5.5

JMG Virtual Consulting S.L, 2014

CERTIFICATION COURSE LPI (LINUX PROFESSIONAL INSTITUTE)

CAS Training, S.L, 2013

AN INTRODUCTION TO INTERACTIVE PROGRAMMING IN PYTHON

Rice University (Coursera), 2013

SYSTEMS CYBERSECURITY

Escola Tècnica Superior D´ Enginyeria, 2008

CSS LAYOUT WITH HTML5

Berkeley University, 2012